Dallas I don't fear you Dallas because she tells me
Dallas no te temo Dallas pues me dice
tweets eh Telling me some
tweets eh Diciéndome cosas un poco
horrible things The thing is that this girl
horribles La Movida es que esta chica
shares this clip of Dallas saying I don't
comparte este clip de Dallas diciendo no
remember if it was Miley Saurus
me acuerdo si era Miley saurus que
dancing and Dallas said Oh if she were my
bailaba y el Dallas decía Oh si fuera mi
girlfriend I would do the beachland no it was
novia le hacía el beachland no que era
like some kind of joke because it was
como una especie de broma porque era
like a meme no and well Dallas explains
como un meme no y bueno Dallas explica
that click in this other video but I do
ese click en este otro vídeo pero es que
n't justify it I said [ __ ] stupid things
no lo justifico dije [__] burradas a
when I was that age and I
mansalva cuando tenía esa edad y
regret it a lot and The girl
arrepiento de ello muchísimo y La chica
says typical of the narcissist everything
dice típico del narcisista todo lo que
he does always has a justification but
él hace siempre tiene justificación pero
what he does in others no Dallas you don't
lo que hace en otros no Dallas no me das
scare me for every video you make of me or
miedo por cada vídeo que tú me hagas o
every answer I'm going to make three
cada respuesta yo voy a hacer tres
videos I'm going to monetize you like you do
vídeos te voy a monetizar como tú haces
What's up Dallas has two
Qué pasa Dallas tiene dos talones de
Achilles heels one is that one the summary of
Aquiles uno es ese el el sumario ese de
that trial and that detail that makes it very
ese juicio y ese detalle que deja
clear the Achilles heel would have his
clarísimo el talón de Aquiles lo tendría
feet blown out by now
reventado los pies ya